# TYLER KOTLOWSKI

# SKILLS

I am a Researcher foremost, Data Analyst, Django Framework, Web Developer and Python Programmer. I've learned many skills, trades, and practices. I am useful in many areas to provide upmost efficiency to those around me. I am a great team member and leader.

# EXPERIENCE

LOASM Technician | USAF | 2012 - 2014

Worked on F-22 stealth aircraft structures for the Air Force.

# Welder | Relco | 2014

Welded food grade stainless steel for cheese manufacturing companies throughout Wisconsin, Minnesota, and Pennsylvania.

### Electrician | Friendship Homes | 2014 – 2015

Worked with raw wiring in mobile homes, including, light fixtures, appliances, circuitry, and other electrical component installations.

### Insurance Agent | Independent | 2015 – 2016

Worked primarily with supplemental insurance and partly with major health plans. Worked with the design/sales of a new insurance platform tool that helped drive business higher.

### Computer Specialist | Best Buy | 2017 – 2017

Worked with all things computers and accessories for mobile devices as well as desktops and laptops.

# Programmer | 2016-Present

Github - https://aithub.com/Nanonzt

Website - http://Kotlowski.graphics

Trading Analyst | Advisor | 2017-PRESENT

# OBJECTIVE

Why hire me? Because I can do many things. I have learned many traits, skills, tools, and knowledge to be incredibly effective at all that I do. If I don't have the answer, I'll find it. I look for patterns, rhythms, series of things, to create more effective paths of execution. I'm more than your average joe.





Best Method Nano.nzt Gmail Work (320) 429 0480

# VOLUNTEERING

I've done environmental clean up in most cities I have lived in. I have volunteered time as security for multiple festivals in Alaska for USAF promotion purposes.

I am a USAF Active Duty Veteran.
I am also an ambassador/advisor to multiple cryptocurrency projects.

# EDUCATION

# HS Diploma | 2012 | YME

# LOASM Cert | 2013 | USAF

Received many aircraft structural certifications. Stealth technology certifications.

Secret clearances.

# Welding Cert | Aug 2014 | Ridgewater, Willmar MN

Graduated 2<sup>nd</sup> in program out of 10 participants. Learned blueprints, architecture, scale models, MIG, TIG, and Stick welding. Most proficient in TIG welding.

### Health and Accident Insurance License | 2015

Minnesota major health license, supplemental insurance license.

# Python | 2017-Today | Florida Institute of Technology

Currently building with Python for data analytics/mining, GUI applications, and webscraping.

### Other Skills and Languages

R, Django, Linux, Unix, Server Administration, Unity 3D, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java

# PROGRAMMING // PROJECTS

### --Clide--

Al Personal Assistant

#### --Sal--

Automated File Merging Program

### --Global Ocean Pollution Research--

Working with R and Unity to produce a real-time animation of the oceans plastic pollution.

(Development)

### --Cryptobot--

Bitcoin trade-bot, automates off my personal trade habits. (Testing)

### INTERESTS

Python/R programming in my free time.

I research cryptocurrency projects and technology.

I spend time with my wife and kids.
I learn new skills.

# GOALS

To live a life of knowledge.

Contribute to great projects.

To retire earlier than most.

# REFERENCES

### Adam Savariego

Long Time Friend / Advisor (320) 226-5082

### **Jerry Streitz**

Advisor (320) 761-3106

### Carlos Esquibel

Long Time Friend (320) 226-8358